<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorial on jpcercal.com</title><link>https://jpcercal.com/en/tags/tutorial/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorial on jpcercal.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>pt</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 06:35:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jpcercal.com/en/tags/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item><title>How to Create a Bidirectional File Sync using Unison</title><link>https://jpcercal.com/en/how-to-create-a-bidirectional-file-sync-using-unison/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 06:35:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jpcercal.com/en/how-to-create-a-bidirectional-file-sync-using-unison/</guid><description>So if you came here I consider you already have a problem to solve, and you are familiar with unison. If this is the case, skip the introduction please.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t, then keep reading as it might clarify a few things before we get started with the how to use unison in order to create a bidirectional (two way) synchronization of two directories.
Introduction To simplify the understanding let&amp;rsquo;s imagine that you have two folders and you want both folders to be synchronized when an event happens such as a new file is created, a file got changed or even a file got deleted.</description></item><item><title>Composer clear cache</title><link>https://jpcercal.com/en/composer-clear-cache/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 20:53:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jpcercal.com/en/composer-clear-cache/</guid><description>Well, today I was facing the follow issue:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11End-of-central-directory signature not found. Either this file is not a zipfile, or it constitutes one disk of a multi-part archive. In the latter case the central directory and zipfile comment will be found on the last disk(s) of this archive. unzip: cannot find zipfile directory in one of /var/www/apps/api/vendor/symfony/symfony/d9b1f549001f508e27a7334590534b83 or /var/www/apps/api/vendor/symfony/symfony/d9b1f549001f508e27a7334590534b83.zip, and cannot find /var/www/apps/api/vendor/symfony/symfony/d9b1f549001f508e27a7334590534b83.</description></item><item><title>How to delete all your Git local branches</title><link>https://jpcercal.com/en/how-to-delete-all-your-git-local-branches/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 11:31:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jpcercal.com/en/how-to-delete-all-your-git-local-branches/</guid><description>Well, from time to time I feel the need of cleaning my local branches, it’s part of my natural workflow and if you need the same you could benefit as well of this handful pipped command below:
1 2 3$ git branch --list | \ egrep --invert-match &amp;quot;(master|gh-pages|\*)&amp;quot; | \ xargs git branch -D   So, I believe the command listed above is self-explained, but if you didn’t understand what’s going on then, here’s the explanation for each on of them:</description></item><item><title>iTerm2 &#43; Zplug = Productivity</title><link>https://jpcercal.com/en/iterm2-plus-zplug-means-productivity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 10:15:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jpcercal.com/en/iterm2-plus-zplug-means-productivity/</guid><description>After spending a long time of my life using the normal terminal I met a new tool called iTerm2 because a friend of mine a few years ago. And, this week I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered the power of zplug. So, here&amp;rsquo;s a brief tutorial on how to get something looking similar to this:
iTerm2 This is a tool like the native app for terminal provided by Apple that has a lot of features that you can just check here.</description></item></channel></rss>